Five alarms, I snooze trying again.
Dragging my feet to who knows when.
Toes burn black under the late scarred.
Faked in a smile, I play the part.
American Idol, stuck in a chair.
Treats collecting, Dufkin dead air.
Promises sold, bought a minimum wage.
Counting the hours in a cage.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
American Idol.
Clipboard kings, they nod and yawn.
Building nothing as time drags on.
Copy stains on an empty plan.
Stuck on posits, change began.
Routine, feel like a disease.
Trading fire for guarantees.
American Idol stuffed in a chair.
Dreams collecting dust and dead air.
Promises sold for minimum wage.
Counting the hours in a cage.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
American Idol.
American Idol, stuck in a jam.
Dream selecting, dusk in dead air.
Promises so far, minimum wage.
Downing the hours in a cage.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh